prankplace.com 2010-05-27

# Privacy Policy

|   
---  
Our Newsletters are jam packed with savings. Be the first to know about new products and promotion.   
  
---  
PrankPlace is committed to superior service, and we proud to offer a 100% Satisfaction Guarantee.  
---  
All your personal information is securely encrypted to provide the most effective defense against identity theft.  
  
### Prankplace.Com Privacy Policy

| We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
---  
  
#### Information Collection and Usage

We respect each site visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.

For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the visitor's domain name.  
  
**This site collects cookies.[(Definition of Cookies)](http://www.netlingo.com/word/cookies.php)**  
**We do NOT ever sell, rent of distribute in anyway information about our customers without their consent. This includes your personal information as well as your email address. WE HATE SPAM!**  
  
#### We do have a weekly email newsletter.

We do publish a weekly "fun-letter" which contains new product annoucements, special offers, sales and other prankplace news. When you order from us, we do add your email address to our customer list so you will automatically receive the fun-letter. If you wish not to receive the fun-letter, simply add a comment to your order, requesting to be excluded.

#### We have an order form.

We require information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and possibly financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). If we have trouble processing an order, we use the information to contact the user. This information is also used:

**•for shipping and billing purposes.  
•to fill customer´s orders.  
•to facilitate our customers' transactions with our third party marketing partners. From time to time we may market certain third party services through our site. Should you choose to accept an offer from a third party, we will pass your relevant personal information, including your name, postal address and your credit/debit card number, to that third party.**

We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors of this feature through a pop-up screen on our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

We publish a newsletter (ezine), and we never sell or share our subscribers' email addresses without their consent.   
  
#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement  
  
#### Conflict Resolution

We are committed to resolving disputes within 24-48 hours. If problems arise, users may contact us by email or telephone.   
  
#### Contact Information

If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us

**Postal Address:**  
PrankPlace.com, LLC  
206 Murphy Road  
Hartford, CT 06114
